<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BaseLine</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="seostr">Search Engine Optimization is the process of enhancing keyword visibility for web page on particular Search Engine. Marketing your website through (SEO) search engine optimization and (SMM) Social Media Marketing is just as important as the mode your website looking and purpose.</string>
    <string name="webDeginStr">Web Designing Company can help you to attract customers. Commonly it is the design of the website which can draw in people but it also has the power to drive them away. </string>
    <string name="webDevelopStr">we are resourceful of tackling it in the high-grade personal manner. Our skillful team up of web designers guide you through with the entire activity of developing and designing a custom website that will suit your particular business status.</string>
    <string name="web">LETS GET STARTED YOUR PROJECT</string>
    <string name="web1">We will advice you to accomplish your goals and to abound your business.</string>
    <string name="aboutus">We offer a full extent of Web Design and Web development Services. Sites, dialogs, online stores, blended media presentations, website change organizations and anything is possible from that point. We speak to impressive specialist in direct web creation organizations for little to medium associations</string>
    <string name="anoutsbaseline">Baseline  Web Development is a web casework and solutions aggregation with a committed development abode in Mohali and attendance in USA we accept been confined our all-around clients. Our website is the a lot of capital affection in online marketing. Quest for connected learning, enhancements and establishing continued appellation plan affiliation with our audience has been the mantra of our success.</string>
    <string name="aboutmain">Baseline Development is a web casework and solutions aggregation with a committed development abode in Mohali and attendance in USA we accept been confined our all-around clients. Our website is the a lot of capital affection in online marketing. Quest for connected learning, enhancements and establishing continued appellation plan affiliation with our audience has been the mantra of our success.

We delivers absolute web casework alignment from custom website architecture to development of circuitous internet systems. We abject our offerings on an compassionate of clients? business requirements and accouterments dependable solutions. We amalgamate or alliance business area ability with technology adequacy and accurate methodologies to bear top superior after-effects in a cost-effective address to aerate your aggressive advantage and productivity.</string>
    <string name="websitedesign">Having a unique web creation is basic bit of the checking and advancing methodology of your business</string>
    <string name="onlinemarket">Our particular exhibiting bunches work to manufacture your progressions, repeat development, and augment your online detectable quality</string>
    <string name="seoopt">Website streamlining is the way toward improving watchword visiblity for site page on specific Search Engine.</string>
</resources>
